(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
It was Sianong’s idea to show you this.
That your brother was arrested
in a drug den and buy-bust operation.
Oh, really?
-What the heck!
-What do you mean no?!
Stop it!
My brother was arrested.
Let’s meet.
I need to talk to you again.
Mikoy…
Your brother has been released.
And the police
won’t press charges anymore.
Return the favor, Mikoy.
Please help me.
Everything must have a contract.
Everything should be documented.
It would be difficult
if we get questioned by the COA.
Oops!
Have you read everything?
And do you understand everything
you read before signing?
Yes.
That I am voluntarily coordinating
with the agency.
Whatever happens to me,
your agency has no liability
and neither does the government.
Meaning, dead or alive,
you wouldn’t care.
Yup. But to be fair,
you will receive a monthly allowance
for working with us
and 13th-month pay as mandated by law.
Plus, 5,000 pesos
for transportation allowance,
and 5,000 pesos for food allowance.
And in case you die in the line of duty,
your family will get
one million pesos and benefits.
Wow!
There’s even a bonus if I die.
Nice.
This is fine.
Do you know how to use that?
Definitely.
Of course.
What are you doing?!
You could kill someone!
How would I know that was a real gun?
Wait!
Someone might hear us here.
Why are you even giving me that?!
I don't need a gun!
I am not going to kill for you.
Didn't you say I'm just a spy?
You’re right. You don't need a gun.
All you need to do is help us
get information about Viktor.
Buddy, hold this first.
Here.
Open it.
This might be something again.
Oh, wait.
This is mine.
Why is it here?
There.
Okay.
This one. You need to find a way
to plant this in Donabel
and Viktor Valtrovi's room.
This device…
For it to work,
you need to connect it.
When the green light appears,
it means connected.
We will hear you on the other side.
The only problem is,
we don’t have ears inside.
As they say,
the secrets of a family are heard
inside the couple's bedroom.
So you need to plant it
inside Donabel and Viktor's room.
Let's go.
Chow.
-Tongits!
-Ah!
-Hey.
-Oh my!
Oh my gosh, honey!
Eww!
Yes. Yes, I'm okay.
-Hey.
-I'll just go to the restroom.
Can you get us some cake, please?
-Thank you!
-Do you want me to go with you?
No, it's okay.
Good day!
Do you think he can do it?
Maybe our new asset is getting cold feet.
I think he'll keep his word.
I hope so.
But I'm sensing
that this new asset is a bit scared.
And I think he might
even turn the tables on us later.
There!
-What?
-I'm picking up a signal.
-Wait.
-Is it activated?
-What?
Is it activated?
Not yet.
But I really heard a signal earlier.
Hey!
Come in.
What happened? Did you plant the device?
No.
I knew it. Our asset
is just being a coward!
Because if not, we won't be able
to get any leads.
I know.
But I was thinking
that planting you’re asking me to do
is dangerous.
I'm sure there's a better way than that.
Oh, really?
So now,
you're the one who decides
what will happen to our investigation?
Just because you've watched
those James Bond movies,
it doesn't mean you know what to do.
You know,
in the short time I got to know Viktor,
he’s really careful.
He even followed me
when I went to the restroom.
If he finds out someone planted
something in his room,
I’m sure I’ll be the first suspect.
And not only that,
our whole operation might be ruined.
I don't know about you, but me,
I don't want to die before my time.
Oh! Look at that!
Looks like he's even better than us.
Why don't you lead instead?
Come on.
You know, if you can’t do this,
just tell us.
Or maybe you're just being a coward.
Do you think I'll be insulted by that?
Hey! Anyone you put
in my position would be scared!
Can you two stop?
All right, if you don't want to plant it,
what's your alternative?
This is what happened.
You know, it's like a mall.
Like the Mall of Asia.
Call me Uncle Vik!
Okay. Uncle Vik!
Oh! You know, if you have a best friend
named Uncle Joey,
it would be perfect!
You know, Uncle Vik and Joey…
About what, Uncle Vik?
An opportunity?
But the question is,
are you open-minded?
And that’s when he offered me
to run Vortex Global Trading.
His import-export company based in Manila.
The same Vortex Global Trading
that you said is being used
by the Moraviano Syndicate.
If I agree to it,
we can gather more information
about their illegal operations.
Have mercy on me!
You're too noisy. I'm still eating!
Huh!
-So what?
-I can't take it anymore.
Huh?
-That's enough.
-What?!
I guess
this idiot has finally learned.
Let this idiot
be an example to all of you!
This is what will happen to you
if you mess
with the Moraviano!
Boss, you have a call.
Looks like he has a point.
Well then, welcome back…
to the Philippines.
B?
Is there a problem?
Do you want to eat?
Uhm, what's good here?
Lechon? Do you want lechon?
It's really delicious, I promise!
Uh, what else?
Laptinaw.
-Budbod!
-Stop the car!
FOR RENT
-Good morning!
-Good morning.
ID?
Four hundred pesos
for the rental and a signature.
ID.
Keep the change.
Thank you!
Okay.
There.
We'll take good care of it.
All right, it's safe here with us.
Hey!
What are you doing?
What?
Are you sure you can handle it?
Are you underestimating my driving skills
because I'm a woman?
No.
Of course not. It's just that…
You know, maybe you're just not used
to the roads here in the Philippines.
The drivers here
are kind of a bit aggressive.
So they want aggressive?
Hold on tight, okay?
Hey!
Nuestra Señora.
This is
Chiara.
Hello.
This church
is the center of our lives here.
Everyone here
gets baptized here,
had the sacrament of confirmation here,
and learned to confess here.
To admit their misdeeds and sins.
Does he have a lot of misdeeds?
Hey!
I could be an awardee
for an exemplary son!
As if.
That's why when the storm hits hard,
when the sea currents are strong,
we all take shelter here
and pray together.
So that Nuestra Señora will protect us.
So throughout your life,
this church will always be there.
And when you die,
this is still the last place
you'll pass through.
You will also be blessed here.
So, even if this is not as big or as grand
as the churches you have in Europe,
we would never trade it for anything.
We really love Nuestra Señora
de Patrocinio de Maria Santisima!
That's why we’re also,
uhm,
loved by her.
That's why everyone who falls in love
gets married here.
What about us?
Can we get married?
Michael D. Pinagpala.
Marriage?
You want to get married?
Right away?
Oh my.
You men are really something.
Your trigger word is the word "marriage".
No, but it's true.
I want to.
You're right.
Why should I keep beating around the bush?
Chiara, I like you.
Chiara, I love you.
I want to be with you
for the rest of my life.
Chiara, I'm absolutely sure.
Chiara.
Mikoy.
Why?
Are you sure?
Look at me.
Ouch!
Why?
You're starting to catch his silliness!
You! You’re the one!
You started it first.
I'm sorry.
-But it's true.
-Stop!
Sorry, Nuestra Señora.
Aren’t you used to having
someone next to you in bed?
Me? Hey. Of course!
I’ll just freshen up.
Hello, everybody!
We are the parents of Chiara.
Is Mikoy there?
Our asset Mikoy confirmed
that the Valtrovi couple
is here in the Philippines.
I cannot explain what the reason is,
but I’m scared for our son.
You’re doing Chiara a favor
because she grew up with lies.
Chiara?
Mikoy?
And she needs to know the truth
about her family.
Sweetheart!
MkvDrama.net